Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPECIAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1902-1966 (Boxes 87-91)
  - Letters of congratulations for publication of Are We Movie Made? 1938 (Folder 6)
  - Correspondence relating to Franklin D. Roosevelt's proposal to reform the Supreme Court, 1937. Includes correspondence with numerous members of Congress (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Controversy over After Seven Years, 1939
    - Unfavorable (Folder 2-3)
    - Favorable (Folder 4)
  - Correspondence relating to Saturday Evening Post serialization of After Seven Years, 1939-1941 (Folder 5)
  - Letters relating to speech, "The Third Term," Stamford, Connecticut, October 1, 1940 (Folder 6)
  - Syndication of newspaper column, 1943-1951 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence relating to newspaper articles about highway slaughter, education in Little Rock and South Carolina, Moley's 25 years in journalism, the human approach to racial integration, "right-to-work" issue and clergy involvement in the public arena, Americans for Constitutional Action, 1953-1958 (Folder 2-7)
  - Letters relating to the 1960 Presidential campaign, 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Letters sent acknowledging congratulations on anniversary of Moley's 30th year with Newsweek, 1963 (Folder 9)
  - Letters of congratulation on birthday, 1966 (Folder 10)
- INDEXED SUBJECT FILE, 1932-1938 (Boxes 92-118)
  Reports, memoranda, letters, telegrams, despatches and instructions, notes, clippings, and printed matter, arranged alphabetically by subject. An item-by-item name and subject index to this series as prepared during the writing of Moley's book After Seven Years (1939) is in the INDEXED CARD FILE
  - 26/1-23 Suggestions for Speeches (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - 27 Agriculture (Folder 3)
  - 28/1-28 Agriculture (Folder 4)
  - 29/1-59 Agriculture (Folder 5-7)
  - 29a/ 1-56 Agriculture (Box 93, Folder 1-5)
  - 29a/ 57-84 Agriculture (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - 29b/ 1-3 Agriculture (Folder 3)
  - 30/1-5 Alaska (Folder 4)
  - 31/1-14 Americanization (Folder 5)
  - 32/1-31 Bonus Bill and Veterans (Folder 6-7)
  - 33/1-7 Chain Store Legislation (Folder 8)
  - 34/1-32 Credits and Corporations (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
  - 34a/ 1-14 Credits and Corporations (Folder 4-6)
  - 34a/ 15-34 Credits and Corporations (Box 96, Folder 1-3)
  - 34b/ 1-42 Credits and Corporations (Folder 4-7)
  - 34b/ 43-92 Credits and Corporations (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
  - 35 Economic Council (Folder 5)
  - 36 Federal Courts (Folder 6)
  - 37/NP Foreign Relations (Folder 7)
  - 37/1-43 Foreign Relations (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
  - 37a/ 1-38 Foreign Relations (Folder 3-5)
  - 37b/ 1-68 Foreign Relations (Box 99, Folder 1-6)
  - 37b/ 69-93 Foreign Relations (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - 37c/ 1-40 Foreign Relations, Russia (Folder 2-3)
  - 37d/1-9 Foreign Relations, German Trade (Folder 4)
  - 37w/ 1-24 Foreign Relations, Nazism (Folder 5-6)
  - 37w/ 25-33 Foreign Relations, Nazism (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - 37x/ 1-11 Foreign Relations, London Monetary and Economic Conference (Folder 2)
  - 37xx/ 1-21A Foreign Relations, London Monetary and Economic Conference (Folder 3-8)
  - 37xx/ 22-88 Foreign Relations, London Monetary and Economic Conference (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - 38/NP Governmental Economy (Folder 3)
  - 38/1-56 Governmental Economy (Folder 4-6)
  - 38a/ 1-66 Governmental Economy (Box 103)
  - 38a/ 67-75 Governmental Economy (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - 39/1-28 International Debts (Folder 2-3)
  - 40/1-45 International Debts (Folder 4-6)
  - 40a/ 1-129 International Debts (Box 105, Folder 1-7)
  - 41 Lippmann, Walter (Box 106, Folder 1-4)
  - 42/1-32 Money (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
  - 42/NP Money (Folder 3)
  - 43/1-69 Money (Folder 4-7)
  - 43/70-114 Money (Box 108, Folder 1-3)
  - 43b/ 1-12 Money Stabilization (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - 43c/ 1-22 Money, Inflation (Folder 2)
  - 44/1-30 Prohibition (Folder 3)
  - 45/NP Power (Folder 4)
  - 45/1-36 Power (Folder 5-6)
  - 45/37-65 Power (Box 110, Folder 1-4)
  - 45/66-96 Power (Box 111, Folder 1-3)
  - 46/1-10 Power, Inland Waterways (Folder 5)
  - 47/1-15 Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Folder 6)
  - 48/1-63 Railroads (Box 112, Folder 1-5)
  - 50/1-61 Unemployment Relief (Box 113, Folder 1-4)
  - 50a/ 1-8 Unemployment Relief (Folder 5)
  - 50a/ 9-36 Unemployment Relief (Box 114, Folder 1-6)
  - 51/1-6 Interior Department (Folder 7)
  - 51/7 Interior Department, Indian Affairs (Folder 8)
  - 51/8-11 Interior Department (Folder 9)
  - 52/1-26 Tariff (Box 115, Folder 1-3)
  - 52a/ 1-32 Tariff (Folder 4-6)
  - 53/1-7 Intra-nationalism (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - 54/1-42 Industrial Recovery (Folder 2-6)
  - 55/1-19 Crime and Crime Prevention (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
  - 56/1-24 Ships and Shipping (Folder 3-4)
  - 57/1-3 Executive Powers (Folder 5)
  - 58/1-15 Social Insurance (Box 118, Folder 1-3)
- SPEECHES, 1932-1960. (Boxes 119-143)
  Speeches, addresses, radio broadcasts, and interviews of Moley, arranged chronologically. See also SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1914-1968
  - Cleveland City Club Address, October 15, 1932 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Rochester Chamber of Commerce Address, January 16, 1933 (Folder 2)
  - Columbia Alumni Address, February 13, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Cincinnati Address, March 17, 1933 (Folder 4)
  - Radio Address on London Conference, May 20, 1933 (Folder 5)
  - Welfare Council Address, May 23, 1933 (Folder 6)
  - Liberal Conference Address, September 8, 1933 (Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Address, October 31, 1933 (Folder 8)
  - American Institute of Banking (Cleveland) Address, November 1, 1933 (?) (no text or notes) (Folder 9)
  - Barnard Alumnae Association Address, November 2, 1933 (Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Address (Amen Corner), November 4, 1933 (Folder 11)
  - Washington and Jefferson College Address, November 4, 1933 (Folder 12)
  - Youngstown Address, November 11, 1933 (no text or notes) (Folder 13)
  - Association of National Advertisers Address, November 14, 1933 (Folder 14)
  - Nebraska Bankers' Association Address, November 16, 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Columbia University Address, December 14, 1933 (Folder 16)
  - NBC Radio Address, December 26, 1933 (Folder 17)
  - Address before the Governor's Conference on Crime, September 30, 1935 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Association of Buying Offices Address, November 26, 1935 (Folder 2)
  - Barnard Alumnae Meeting Address, March 4, 1936 (Folder 3)
  - Scranton Century Club Address, March 13, 1936 (Folder 4)
  - Young Democrats Address, April 13, 1936 (?), (suggestions for address) (Folder 5)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Address, April 24, 1936 (Folder 6)
  - New York National Economy League Address, May 26, 1936 (Folder 7)
  - CBS Radio Address, May 29, 1936 (Folder 8)
  - Advertising Federation of America Address, July 1, 1936 (Folder 9)
  - NBC Radio Broadcast, September 23, 1936 (Folder 10)
  - Association of National Advertisers Address, October 9, 1936 (Folder 11)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Address, December 10, 1936 (Folder 12)
  - National Federation of Sales Executives Address, December 15, 1936 (Folder 13)
  - Santa Barbara Address, January 4, 1937 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - CBS Bank Program Address, February 26, 1937 (Folder 2)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies Address, April 30, 1937 (Folder 3)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Movie Statement, April 1937 (Folder 4)
  - Toledo Chamber of Commerce Address, May 7, 1937 (Folder 5)
  - University of Toledo Address, May 17, 1937 (Folder 6)
  - Station WOR Address, May 13, 1937 (Folder 7)
  - National Association of Shirt and Pajama Manufacturers Address, May 17, 1927 (Folder 8)
  - Illinois Bankers' Association Address, May 25, 1937 (Folder 9)
  - American Defense Society Address, June 14, 1937 (Folder 10)
  - Hardware Manufacturers Statistical Association Address, September 16, 1937 (Folder 11)
  - Passaic Community Forum Address, September 27, 1937 (Folder 12)
  - American Institute of Accountants Address, October 19, 1937 (Folder 13)
  - Illinois Manufacturers' Costs Association Address, October 26, 1937 (Folder 14)
  - United States Brewers' Association Address, October 27, 1937 (Folder 15)
  - Boston Beacon Society Address, November 6, 1937 (no text or notes) (Folder 16)
  - Syracuse University Address, November 1937 (Folder 17)
  - Temple Beth-El Address, November 10, 1937 (Folder 18)
  - Station KTMS Radio Interview, November 29, 1937 (Folder 19)
  - Cleveland Advertising Club Address, December 15, 1937 (Folder 20)
  - Allie S. Freed Eulogy, January 14, 1938 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Club Address, February 12, 1938 (Folder 2)
  - La Grange Legion Address, February 13, 1938 (Folder 3)
  - Eastern Illinois State Teachers College Address, February 14, 1938 (Folder 4)
  - Newton Community Forum Address, February 20, 1938 (Folder 5)
  - Waterbury, Conn., Radio Address, February 28, 1938 (Folder 6)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, March 3, 1938 (Folder 7)
  - New York City Town Hall Address, March 30, 1938 (Folder 8)
  - Santa Barbara Radio Address, April 26, 1938 (Folder 9)
  - Meetings with Newsweek advertisers in San Francisco and Denver, April 1938 (Folder 10)
  - Poor Richard Club Address, May 10, 1938 (Folder 11)
  - Detroit Economic Club Address, May 16, 1938 (Folder 12)
  - National Association of Purchasing Agents Address, May 23, 1938 (Folder 13)
  - National Conference of State Liquor Administrators Address, June 13, 1938 (Folder 14)
  - California Commonwealth Club Address, June 17, 1938 (Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Address, June 18, 1938 (Folder 16)
  - Ohio University Address, July 14, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 17)
  - Committee of One Hundred Address (Painesville, Ohio), August 2, 1938 (Folder 18)
  - Station WMCA Radio Address (New York City), September 17, 1938, (and other material for John O'Connor Campaign) (Folder 19)
  - Newark Advertising Club Address, October 20, 1938 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - New York Herald Tribune Forum Address, October 25, 1938 (Folder 2)
  - G. P. Putnam's Sons Address, October 27, 1938 (Folder 3)
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers Address (Pittsfield, MA), November 1, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Syracuse Association of Credit Men Address, November 8, 1938 (Folder 5)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce Address, November 9, 1938 (Folder 6)
  - Graduate Teachers College Address (Winnetka, IL), November 9, 1938 (Folder 7)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club Address, November 10, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 8)
  - Chicago Athletic Association Address, November 10, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 9)
  - Madison Civics Club Address, November 12, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs Address, November 14, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 11)
  - Life Advertisers Association Address, November 16, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 12)
  - New York Canadian Club Address, December 6, 1938 (Folder 13)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Address, December 7, 1938 (Folder 14)
  - Eastern Industrial Advertisers Address, December 9, 1938 (no text or notes) (Folder 15)
  - Station WJZ Radio Address (New York City), December 11, 1938 (Folder 16)
  - Reformed Church Men's Club Address (Bronxville), January 10, 1939 (Folder 17)
  - Station WEVD Radio Debate (New York City), February 22, 1939 (Folder 18)
  - Detroit and Flint Addresses (Michigan), May 25 and 26, 1939 (Folder 19)
  - National Industrial Advertisers Association Address, September 20, 1939 (Folder 20)
  - Insurance Advertising Conference Address, October 2, 1939 (Folder 21)
  - Cleveland Advertising Club Address, October 4, 1939 (Folder 22)
  - New York Advertising Club Address, October 13, 1939 (Folder 23)
  - Hartford Chamber of Commerce Address, October 25, 1939 (Folder 24)
  - Yale Talk, October 30, 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Harvard Club Address, November 3, 1939 (Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Transportation Club Address, November 16, 1939 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Kenmore High School Teachers Association Address (Kenmore, NY), November 17, 1939 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Boston Commercial Club Address, November 21, 1939 (Folder 3)
  - Hazelton City Teachers Library Association Address (PA), November 22, 1939 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Worcester Economic Club Address, November 27, 1939 (Folder 5)
  - Detroit Bankers Club Address, November 30, 1939 (no text or notes) (Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin Manufacturers' Association Address (PA), November 22, 1939 (no text or notes) (Folder 7)
  - Youngstown Chamber of Commerce Address, December 5, 1939 (Folder 8)
  - Peoria Association of Commerce Address, December 7, 1939 (Folder 9)
  - Toledo Rotary Club Address, January 8, 1940 (Folder 10)
  - National Retail Furniture Association Address, January 10, 1940 (Folder 11)
  - Athenaeum Address (Summit, NJ), January 11, 1940 (Folder 12)
  - Melrose Teachers' Public Forum Address, January 17, 1940 (Folder 13)
  - Thayer Academy Alumni Association Address, January 18, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Credit Men's Association of Eastern Pennsylvania Address, January 19, 1940 (Folder 15)
  - Bridgeport University Club Address, February 9, 1940 (Folder 16)
  - Chicago Dental Society Address, February 12, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 17)
  - Indianapolis Contemporary Club Address, February 14, 1940 (Folder 18)
  - La Grange Legion Address (IL), February 18, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 19)
  - Grinnell College Address, February 19, 1940 (Folder 20)
  - Milwaukee Rotary Club Address, February 20, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 21)
  - Milwaukee City Club Address, February 20, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 22)
  - Northwestern University Address, February 21, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 23)
  - Fort Smith Junior College Address, February 22, 1940 (Folder 24)
  - San Antonio Open Forum, February 26, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 25)
  - New York City Town Hall Address, March 5, 1940 (Folder 26)
  - Jamestown Civic Forum Address (NY), March 12, 1940 (Folder 27)
  - New York Bond Club Address, April 24, 1940 (Folder 28)
  - Industrial Advertisers Association Address, June 25, 1940 (Folder 29)
  - California Address, Summer 1940 (Folder 30)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, September 17, 1940 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis Advertising Club Address, September 18, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Stamford Associated Willkie Clubs Address (Conn.), October 1, 1940. See also SPECIAL CORRESPONDENCE (Folder 3)
  - Boston Chamber of Commerce Address, October 7, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey Address, October 7, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 5)
  - Port Washington Address (Long Island), October 11, 1940 (Folder 6)
  - Moline After Dinner Club Address, October 14, 1940 (Folder 7)
  - Republican Women of Delaware Address, October 16, 1940 (Folder 8)
  - Virginia Democrats for Willkie Address, October 16, 1940 (Folder 9)
  - New York City Address, October 23, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - Rochester, New York Address, October 24, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 11)
  - Cleveland Addresses, October 25 and 26, 1940 (Folder 12)
  - Manhattan Campaign Committee Address, October 29, 1940 (no text or notes) (Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Town Hall Address, October 31, 1940 (Folder 14)
  - Women's National Republican Club Address, November 1, 1940 (Folder 15)
  - Election Eve Broadcast, November 4, 1940 (Folder 16)
  - Invitations to speak during Willkie Campaign, 1940 (not accepted) (Folder 17)
  - First Presbyterian Church Address (Santa Barbara), December 29, 1940 (Folder 18)
  - Cincinnati Advertising Club Address, January 22, 1941 (Folder 19)
  - Indianapolis Advertising Club Address, January 23, 1941 (Folder 20)
  - Columbus Advertising Club Address, January 24, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 21)
  - Barrington Town-Warming Address (Illinois), January 17, 1941 (no text or notes) (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - United Charities Campaign Address, February 10, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Advertising Club Address, February 26, 1941 (Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Chamber of Commerce Address, February 28, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Life Underwriters' Association of New York Address, March 27, 1941 (Folder 5)
  - Chicago Executives' Club Address, April 18, 1941 (Folder 6)
  - National Industrial Advertising Association Address, April 18, 1941 (Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Manufacturers' Association Address, May 10, 1941 (Folder 8)
  - Harvard Medical Society of New York Address, May 31, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 9)
  - New York Union League Club Address, May 15, 1941 (Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Advertising Club Address, May 27, 1941 (Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Grade Crude Oil Association Address, June 19, 1941 (Folder 12)
  - Lancaster Rotary Club Address, August 21, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 13)
  - Financial Advertisers' Association Address, September 8, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Iowa Bankers' Association Address, September 10, 1941 (cancelled) (Folder 15)
  - National Hardwood Lumber Association Address, September 18, 1941 (Folder 16)
  - Philadelphia Sales Managers' Association Address, October 20, 1941 (no text or notes) (Folder 17)
  - Indiana Association of Personal Finance Companies Address, November 5, 1941 (Folder 18)
  - Chicago Sales Executives Club Address, November 13, 1941 (Folder 19)
  - Cleveland Media Group Address, January 26, 1942 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - New York Sales Managers' Club Address, February 6, 1942 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Toledo Chamber of Commerce Address, February 19, 1942 (Folder 3)
  - Wesleyan University Address, March 2, 1942 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Boston Real Estate Exchange Address, March 4, 1942 (Folder 5)
  - Rochester Yale Club Address, March 20, 1942 (Folder 6)
  - Buffalo Aero Club Address, March 27, 1942 (Folder 7)
  - St. Paul Advertising Club Address, March 28, 1942 (Folder 8)
  - American Hardware Manufacturers' Association Address, April 22, 1942 (Folder 9)
  - Indiana Bankers' Association Address, May 13, 1942 (Folder 10)
  - Western Trip, September 1942 (Folder 11)
  - Baltimore Advertising Club Address, October 21, 1942 (Folder 12)
  - Iowa Bankers' Association Address, October 26, 1942 (Folder 13)
  - Industrial Marketers of Cleveland Address, October 28, 1942 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce Address, November 10, 1942 (Folder 15)
  - Syracuse Advertising Club Address, November 18, 1942 (Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Speeches, 1943 (Folder 17)
  - Shreveport Chamber of Commerce Address, January 22, 1943 (Folder 18)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, February 9, 1943 (Folder 19)
  - Friend of the Claremont Colleges Address, February 19, 1943 (Folder 20)
  - Minneapolis Association of Sales Managers Address, March 24, 1943 (no text or notes) (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Chamber of Commerce Address, March 26, 1943 (Folder 2)
  - Baldwin-Wallace College Address, May 31, 1943 (Folder 3)
  - Chicago Rotary Club Address, September 14, 1943 (Folder 4)
  - National Physicians Committee Address, October 4, 1943 (no text or notes) (Folder 5)
  - Disston and Sonds Address, October 8, 1943 (Folder 6)
  - Carrier Institute of Business Address, October 11, 1943 (Folder 7)
  - American Institute of Steel Construction Address, October 19, 1943 (Folder 8)
  - New York Sales Managers' Club Address, October 22, 1943 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies Address, November 5, 1943 (Folder 11)
  - Montreal Advertising and Sales Executives Club Address, December 1, 1943 (Folder 12)
  - Portland Address, December 18, 1943 (no text or notes) (Folder 13)
  - San Francisco Advertising Club Address, December 22, 1943 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Town Hall Address, December 27, 1943 (no text or notes) (Folder 15)
  - Cuvier Press Club Address, January 19, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 16)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, January 20, 1944 (Folder 17)
  - University School Commencement Address (Cleveland, Ohio), January 31, 1944 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Texas Company Address, February 9, 1944 (Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Rotary Club Address, March 8, 1944 (Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Advertising Club Address, March 14, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Independent Petroleum Association of America Address, April 29, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 5)
  - Ohio State Bar Association Address, May 12, 1944 (Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia City Business Club Address, August 11, 1944 (Folder 7)
  - Portland Chamber of Commerce Address, September 18, 1944 (Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Rotary Club Address, September 29, 1944 (Folder 9)
  - National Stationers Association Address, October 3, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - New York Financial Advertisers Address, October 18, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 11)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, October 25, 1944 (Folder 12)
  - Detroit Adcraft Club Address, October 26, 1944 (?) (Folder 13)
  - Toledo Club Address, October 27, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Texaco Round Table Address, November 1, 1944 (no text or notes) (Folder 15)
  - National Association of Public Relations Council Address, November 16, 1944 (Folder 16)
  - Tax Foundation Address, December 6, 1944 (Folder 17)
  - Indiana State Bar Association Address, January 13, 1945 (Folder 18)
  - Economic Club of Southwestern Michigan Address, January 24, 1945 (no text or notes) (Folder 19)
  - Milwaukee Advertising Club Address, January 25, 1945 (Folder 20)
  - Republican Club of the 9th A.D. Address, March 16, 1945 (Folder 21)
  - Newark Address, April 24, 1945 (Folder 22)
  - American Council on Public Relations Committee Address, May 9, 1945 (no text or notes) (Folder 23)
  - America's Town Meeting of the Air Address, May 31, 1945 (Folder 24)
  - Los Angeles Town Hall Address, June 25, 1945 (Folder 25)
  - Norwalk, Conn. Address, August 30, 1945 (no test or notes) (Folder 26)
  - Ohio Society of New York Address, October 8, 1945 (Folder 27)
  - Peoria Advertising and Selling Club Address, October 15, 1945 (Folder 28)
  - Ohio Public Expenditure Council Address, November 16, 1945 (no text or notes) (Folder 29)
  - Republican Committee of One Hundred Address, January 8, 1946 (no text or notes) (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club Address, January 31, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Kansas City Advertising and Sales Executives Club Address, February 4, 1946 (Folder 3)
  - New York Sales Managers' Club Address, March 1, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania State Chamber of Commerce Address, March 20, 1946 (Folder 5)
  - United States Independent Telephone Association Address, April 6, 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Minneapolis Sales Managers' Club Address, April 17, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 7)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, April 18, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 8)
  - Women's National Republican Club Address, April 23, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 9)
  - Indianapolis Rotary Club Address, May 21, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - Chicago Commercial Club Address, May 22, 1946 (Folder 11)
  - National Federation of Sales Executives Address, May 22, 1946 (Folder 12)
  - American Psychiatric Association Address, May 29, 1946 (Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles Advertising Club Address, August 13, 1946 (Folder 14)
  - Nebraska State Bankers Association Address, October 12, 1946 (Folder 15)
  - Providence Sales Managers' Club Address, October 14, 1946 (Folder 16)
  - American Marketing Association Address, October 23, 1946 (Folder 17)
  - Limited Price Variety Stores Association Address, November 6, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 18)
  - Minneapolis Advertising Club Address, November 20, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 19)
  - Saint Paul Association of Commerce Address, November 20, 1946 (no text or notes) (Folder 20)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Address, December 4, 1946 (Folder 21)